exforsys.com 2004-12-07

# Exforsys.com Privacy

Exforsys.com is committed to protecting your privacy and to providing technology that gives you a secure online experience. The majority of the website can be viewed without giving us any information about yourself. However for certain areas of the website and for certain functions you are required to enter personal information. This privacy statement explains the data we collect and its use in these situations.

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you or allows us to contact you. Generally but not limited to, this information is requested when you sign up to become a member of Exforsys.com and when you send us feedback.

Any Job Postings and training related information from any company ads are not paid advertisements and Exforsys Inc should not be held liable as a result of any outcome of the relationship between that consulting company and the job seeker.

Personal information collected from Exforsys.com often is limited to name, email address, location but may from time to time include other information when needed to provide a service that you requested.

We use your personal information to contact you when you have a query and to supply you with a newsletter if you request one. 

We occasionally use third party companies to provide services on our behalf. We will only provide those companies the information they require to deliver their service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

Exforsys.com protects the security of your personal information and honors your choice for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction.

Your personal information is never shared outside Exforsys.com without your permission, except under conditions explained above.

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your username and password to Exforsys.com, so do not share these with others.

To enable us to monitor and improve the site, we may gather certain information about you when you use the website, including details of your Operating system: e.g., Windows, DOS, Macintosh, or UNIX; Browser version and type: e.g., Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer; Browser language: e.g., Java or Unix; Internet Service Provider (ISP): e.g., Mind Spring or AOL.

Your IP address: a unique number assigned to every computer on the Internet. The type of information that Exforsys.com can infer from the IP address is a geographic location. Your domain: e.g., .COM, net, or .edu. This is standard information that is available with all communication sent on the Internet.

We may use cookies only to store information such as your User ID and your session identifiers to enable us to identify whether you are registered on to the site and, if so, to shortcut your access to the site. We will only read cookies from your cookie file placed there through your web browser's interaction with the site. Our site may link to other web sites and we are not responsible for their data policies or procedures or their content.

We endeavor to take all reasonable steps to protect your personal Data including the use of encryption technology, but Exforsys.com cannot guarantee the security of any data that you disclose online.
